# **ANUJ VERMA**

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Detailed oriented and self motivated software professional with over 10 years experience in analysis, design and development.

Passionate for result-oriented approach with a focus on quality and user experience.

Product design, architect and leading development with focus on tracking, AB testing, SEO and adOPs are some of the areas of expertise.

# **WORK HISTORY**

<u>dubizzle, OLX Group</u> - Dubai, UAE Senior Software Engineer (October 2016 - Till Date)

- Developed Component library based on atomic design principles.
- Setup CI/CD for all the frontend apps including packages in monorepo.
- Developed on a Content-First approach for home pages, chat platform integration and payment module are some notable achievements.
- Actively managing SEO and AdOps.

**CDK Global** - Pune, India

Senior Software Engineer (Mar 2014 - October 2016)

- Worked with teams to build central IAM with oAuth.
- Developed chat service implementation with mongooselM.
- Led the development team for developing soft phone desktop apps with chat.

Entrib Technologies - Pune, India

Senior Software Engineer (June 2012 - Feb 2014)

- Completed design concepts for consumer and enterprise apps.
- Led HTML5 Mobile apps development.

Infosys - Pune, India

Software Engineer (Sept 2008 - June 2012)

- Developed a Set-top box application for monitoring viewers' viewing habits and helps delivering targeted ads to them.
- T9 dictionary implementation for TV Remote.

# **EDUCATION**

# **B.Tech Computer Science and Engineering**

Uttar Pradesh Technical University 2004-2008

#### **REFERENCES**

references available on request

#### **CONTACT**

Phone: +971-5225453595

Email: anujverma000@gmail.com

Blog: anujverma.netlify.com

Github: github.com/anujverma000

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/anujverma000

#### SKILLS

NodeJs & Express

React & Redux, Redux Toolkit

NextJs

React Native

HTML, Pug, Handlebars

Javascript, ES6, JQuery

CSS, SASS, Styled Components

Webpack, Rollup, Grunt, Gulp

GraphQL

ElectronJS

Serverless

CI & CD

Atomic Design

**AdOps** 

SE<sub>0</sub>

# **SOFT SKILLS**

Collaboration

Communication

Leadership

**Problem Solving** 

Scrum Master

## **PROJECTS**

shopworx.io

nextplane.net

federationexchange.com

# **LANGUAGES**

English Hindi